abnamro.com 2009-01-22

# ABN AMRO - Privacy Statement

This web site is administered by ABN AMRO Bank N.V., with its principal place of business located at Gustav Mahlerlaan 10, Amsterdam (P.O. Box 283, 1000 EA), The Netherlands, and registered in the Amsterdam Trade Registry under number 33002587 ("ABN AMRO"). 

When you visit this web site ABN AMRO may collect personal data about you, either directly (where you are asked to provide the data) or indirectly. ABN AMRO will, however, only use these personal data in accordance with the purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement and is committed to safeguarding the personal information collected. This statement sets out the purposes of ABN AMRO's data processing in respect of this web site, the use of cookies and how to effect your rights in respect of your personal data. 

**Purposes of Processing**

ABN AMRO collects and processes information about customers and visitors to its web site to conduct its business, to inform and make available products and services that may be of interest to you and for the development of web statistics. The information you provide will be used to contact you when necessary, e.g. to notify you about functionality changes to the web site and to offer services that you may find helpful (provided you have not opted out to receive such services). 

ATTENTION: 

Check whether these purposes are applicable to your processing activities or whether other purposes should be added. 

The ways in which ABN AMRO collects and uses personal data, through this web site and otherwise, are specifically regulated by the [ insert name of local privacy code of conduct that is applicable, if any, and if possible, add link]. 

ATTENTION: 

Check whether local legislation or processing activities require the above paragraph, if not delete this paragraph 

**Sensitive Data**

ABN AMRO does not seek to collect sensitive personal data (such as data revealing political opinions, religious beliefs, health or other matters) through this site. If ABN AMRO does seek to collect such data, your prior (explicit) consent hereto will be asked. Please note that, by providing ABN AMRO with unsolicited sensitive personal data you (explicitly) consent to our using those data as described above. 

**Cookies**

ABN AMRO may collect and analyse information in connection with the use of his web site, such as domain name, the number of hits, the pages visited, previous/subsequent sites visited and length of user session. This information may be collected by using cookies. A cookie is a small text file containing relevant information which our webpage-server can extract from your browser. Our webpage-server may only require cookies that relate to information that has been exchanged between you and ABN AMRO through internet. Cookies not containing any security sensitive information can be stored on your hard disk in such a manner that they are available during the next visit. The only cookie that is saved from the secured domain on the hard disk is the cookie that is used for retaining the bank account- and pass number on the login page. You can allow the use of cookies or prevent this by changing the settings of your browser. If you prevent the use of cookies, the mentioned information shall no longer be stored by your browser and with every visit your information shall be required and shall have to be completed again. Furthermore, the use of Internet Banking is not possible without the use of cookies. However, use of the open domain (<http://www.abnamro.nl/>) through the browser is possible without the use of cookies. Specific settings regarding cookies depend on the type of browser. 

**Third Party Sites**

Please note that this Privacy Statement does not extend to third party sites linked to this web site. 

How to Effect Your Rights; How to Contact ABN AMRO 

If you do not wish to receive any marketing messages from ABN AMRO, you can contact us via [ insert you local address/phone number/e-mailaddress via which requests will be processed]. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our data processing activities or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us via [ insert you local address/phone number/e-mailaddress via which requests will be processed]. 

**Amendments**

ABN AMRO reserves the right to modify sections of this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes.
